[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community
So for each model order that we might consider,
对于每一个我们可能考虑到的模型的次数
for example, a linear model or
举例来说 一个线性模型 或者
we also talked about using a quadratic model,
我们同样讨论过使用一个二次模型
all the way up to our very crazy, 13th order polynomial.
一直到我们所讨论的 非常疯狂的 13次多项式
And of course, we could consider even higher order models.
当然 我们甚至也可以考虑更加高次的模型
Well, what happens to test error?
好的 那么测试损失会发生什么呢？
Sorry, I don't mean test error.
抱歉 我想说的不是测试损失
Let's start with training error.
让我们从训练损失开始
A lot easier to think about.
这考虑起来要容易许多
So training error.
所以训练损失
As we increase the model order, well, that models able
当我们增加模型的次数时 这样的模型能够
to better and better fit the observations in that training dataset.
更好地拟合我们在训练集中的观测值
So what we're gonna have is we're gonna have that our training error
所以我们将会看到的是 我们的训练损失
decreases with increasing model order.
会随着模型次数的上升而下降
So remember the curves that we had.
记住我们所画出的这条曲线
We had the residual sum of squares associated with that linear fit,
我们可以看到残差平方和的变化 关于线性拟合
quadratic fit, all the way up to the 13th order polynomial that basically hit
二次拟合 一直到13次多项式的拟合 这基本上符合了
each one of those observations.
我们每一个的观测值
So, we saw that a residual sum of squares was going down and down and down.
所以我们可以看到 残差平方和在不断地下降
So that's true even if we hold out some observations and
这个趋势即使当我们排除了一些观测值的时候也成立
just look at our training dataset.
也就是我们仅仅着眼于训练集
So we're gonna have our training error decreasing and
所以我们会看到我们的训练损失在下降
decreasing as we increase the flexibility of the model.
当我们增加模型的灵活性的时候不断地下降
But, so let's just annotate this as being our training error,
让我们把这条曲线标注为我们的训练损失
particularly for our estimated model parameters w hat.
特别地 是关于我们所估计的模型参数 w帽的损失
So let's be clear about what we mean by w hat.
现在让我们来弄清楚w 帽究竟代表了什么
So for every model complexity such as linear model, quadratic model, and so on.
对于每一个复杂度层次的模型 比如线性模型 二次模型等等
What we're gonna do is we're gonna optimize and
我们所要做的 就是去最优化
find the parameters w hat for the linear model.
并且为线性模型找到一组参数w 帽
We're searching over all possible lines minimizing the training error.
我们会在所有可能的直线当中搜索 搜索那条最小化训练损失的线
Remember that's what we said,
还记得我们所说过的吗
couple slides ago we said that the way we estimate our model is we're gonna
在好几页幻灯片之前我们曾经说过 我们用来估计模型的方法就是
minimize the air on that observations in our training dataset.
最小化与我们的训练集上观测值的误差
So that's how we get w hat for the linear model,
这就是我们如何获得线性模型的参数w 帽的方法
and we compute the training error associated with that w hat.
然后我们就用w 帽去计算训练损失
Then we look at all possible quadratic fits.
接下来让我们考察所有可能的二次曲线拟合
Minimize the training error for over all the quadratic fits,
在所有的二次曲线上最小化训练损失
that's how we get w hat for the quadratic model.
这就是我们得到二次曲线的w 帽的方法
And then we plot the training error associated with the w hat for
然后我们画出关于w hat的训练损失
the quadratic model and so on.
那些二次曲线的w 帽等等诸如此类
Well, we can also talk about test error, but
好的 我们同样也可以来讨论测试损失 但是
here it's a little bit more complicated because what do we think is gonna
这里会稍稍地复杂一些 让我们来考虑一下
happen as we increase and increase our model order?
当我们增加模型的次数的时候 测试损失会发生什么呢？
Well, what we saw, if you remember that 13th order polynomial fit,
如果你还记得那个13次多项式拟合的模型 我们所看到的是
that really crazy wiggly line, we had really, really bad predictions.
那条疯狂而扭曲的曲线 所作出的预测是十分糟糕的
So when we think about holding out our test data, fitting a 13th order
所以当我们考虑把测试集排除在外 拟合13次多项式模型的时候
polynomial just on the training data, we're gonna get some wiggly, crazy fit.
仅仅使用训练数据 我们会看到一条扭曲而疯狂的拟合曲线
And then when we look at those test observations, those houses that we
接着当我们考察测试集中的观测数据 就是那些我们
held out, we're probably gonna have very poor predictions of those actual values.
排除在外的数据 我们可能会发现相比那些实际的数据 我们的预测非常糟糕
So what we're gonna expect is that at some point,
所以符合我们预期的是 在某一个点上
our test error is likely to increase.
我们的测试损失很可能会开始上升
So the curves for test error tend to look something like the following
所以测试损失的函数曲线 很可能看上去像下面这样
where maybe the error is going down for some period of time but after a point
在某些时间段当中测试损失可能是下降的 但是超过一个点之后
The error starts to increase again.
损失开始重新地上升
So here this curve is our test error for
这就是测试损失的变化曲线
these fitted models,
关于我们所拟合的这些模型
where the models were fit
这些模型
using the training data.
是用训练数据来拟合的
So these are what curves tend to look like for training error and
这些曲线就是训练损失
test error as a function of model complexity, and
和测试损失关于模型复杂度的函数关系所应该呈现的样子
how we think about using these ideas to actually select the model or
那么我们如何使用这些思想 去实际上选择一个模型
the complexity of the model that we should use for making our predictions.
或者说模型的复杂度 然后基于我们选择的模型去作出预测
We're gonna discuss in a lot more detail in the regression and
我们会在之后的课程中更加深入地讨论这些细节 在回归分析的课程
classification courses.
以及分类的课程中
[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community